mariaandros.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Maria Andros

Last updated May 24, 2018.

Maria Andros International (“Maria Andros International”) operates http://www.mariaandros.com and may operate other websites. It is Maria Andros International’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Maria Andros International collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Maria Andros International’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Maria Andros International’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Maria Andros International may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Maria Andros International’s also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://www.mariaandros.com blogs/sites. Maria Andros International’s only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Maria Andros International’s websites choose to interact with Maria Andros International in ways that require Maria Andros International to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Maria Andros International gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at http://www.mariaandros.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Maria Andros International are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Maria Andros International collects such information only in so far as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Maria Andros International. Maria Andros International does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**GDPR Compliance**

Your data will be retained until you request us to delete it, or until 18 months passes without any action from you including opening an email, purchasing a product, and visiting our website pages. If you provide us with any of your personal information such as your name, email, phone number, address, or credit card for a purchase, then you have the right to request to view all of the information you’ve provided, to correct any of your information, or request us to delete it from our database. You can exercise this right by clicking on the link you’ll find for data request in the footer of our website as well as in the footer of each email.

If you have a concern about how the data that you’ve provided is being used, or if you have a complaint you’d like to file regarding your personal information, you can contact us at the email support@mariaandros.com.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Maria Andros International may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Maria Andros International may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Maria Andros International does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.  
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Maria Andros International discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Maria Andros International’s behalf or to provide services available at Maria Andros International’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Maria Andros International’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Maria Andros International will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Maria Andros International discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Maria Andros International believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Maria Andros International, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Maria Andros International website and have supplied your email address, Maria Andros International may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with Maria Andros International’s events and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Maria Andros International takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Maria Andros International uses cookies to help Maria Andros International identify and track visitors, their usage of Maria Andros International’s website, and their website access preferences. Maria Andros International visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Maria Andros International’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Maria Andros International’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Maria Andros International, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Maria Andros International goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Maria Andros International may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies byMaria Andros International and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Maria Andros International may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Maria Andros International’s sole discretion. Maria Andros International encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a http://www.mariaandros.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Questions Or Comments About Our Privacy Policy

Maria Andros International is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors and using the information you provide us responsibly. Personal data privacy is a new and rapidly changing area. We are committed to meeting these evolving challenges. If you have any questions or comments, please contact us. We’d be pleased to answer your questions and would like to know any concerns or suggestions you might have.
